

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Programing: C,C++,Java,JSP

Database :- Oracle, MySql , Mongodb Front End :- HTML5 ,CSS3,Bootstrap,

SASS

Full Stack Web Development

Market Research. Problem Solving Project Management.

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

# CONTACT

P: +91 93730 76931 E: anikurhade2002@gmail.com

# SOCIAL



anikurhade



# ANIRUDHA KURHADE

# PROGRAMMMER

#### **ABOUT**

I am 19 Year Student, Currently Persuing My Bachelors In Computer Engineering At Pune. I am A Web Developer And Find Myself Congerial while Creating Pleasing And Charming Website. I am Not Only A Philomath But Also A Technophile And Loves To Loiter My Time In Listening EDM's and Having a Security Research In Various Vulnerabilities.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

RESEARCH ANALYST

Hack X Security| Sept 2020 - Mar 2021

- Managed And Researched About Company Clients And Competitors.
- Designed Strategy And Work-Plan For Campus Ambassadors
- Acted As A Lubricant In various Admin As Well As Marketing Sections.

# STUDENT PARTNER

Give My Certificate | Nov 2020 - May 2021

- Created Various Campus Contact for Company .
- Help Them To Grow In My Campus.
- Worked On Various Reach Making Strategy.

## **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Vishwakarma Institute Of Information Technology | 2021 -2024

DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Government Polytechnic Pune | 2018 -2021

Per:- 96.47%

#### **AWARDS**

SILVER MEADALIST
Government Polytechnic Pune | Dec 2021

HALL OF FAME
OSI Soft | Lemi | Pabio .

ACKNOWLEDGMENT BY
Qualcomm , Dell;
Bounty By :- Pabio, Wallaram.